Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - African National Congress [South Africa]. Serial issues (Sechaba), 1970-1973 (Folder 51: 39)
  - Afro-Americans against the War in Vietnam. Flyers and clippings, 1966 (Folder 51: 40)
  - Air War Study Group [Cornell University]. Printed report (The Air War in Indochina), 1972 (Folder 51: 41)
  - Akron Industrial Union Council [Akron, Ohio]. Correspondence, circulars, flyers, resolutions, grievance records, and financial and other internal documents, 1937-1941. (Folder 52: 1)
    Includes records of the Workers Alliance of Summit County, Ohio
  - Albania. Albanian government pamphlet (Marxist-Leninist Ideology Will Certainly Overcome Revisionism), 1964 (Folder 52: 2)
  - Albanian Affairs Study Group [New York City]. Newsletters (Albania Report), 1970-1972 (Folder 52: 3)
  - Alexander Defense Committee [re Neville Alexander, South Africa]. Letters, flyers and newsletters, 1965-1967 (Folder 52: 4)
  - All Points of View [book distributor, San Antonio, Texas]. Catalogs, 1973 (Folder 52: 5)
  - Alliance for Action [San Francisco]. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 52: 6)
  - The Ally [GI newspaper, Berkeley]. Circular letter, 1967 (Folder 52: 7)
  - Amerasia. Serial issues of the publication, and pamphlet (The Shocking Story of the Amerasia Case), 1937-1950 (Folder 52: 8)
  - America First Committee. American Legion pamphlet (Subversive Activities in America First Committee in California), 1941 (Folder 52: 9)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Printed appeal and clipping, 1968 (Folder 52: 10)
  - American Artists' Congress. Printed appeal, journal articles, and HUAC memorandum, 1935-ca. 1942 (Folder 52: 11)
  - American Association for the United Nations. Leaflet, and American Legion pamphlet (Preliminary Report on the American Association for the United Nations, Inc.), 1955 (Folder 52: 12)
  - American Association of University Professors. Clipping and printed report, 1963-1967 (Folder 52: 13)
  - American Association to Combat Fascism, Racism and Anti-Semitism. Newsletter (Fact Memorandum), 1971 (Folder 52: 14)
  - American Bar Association. Correspondence and reports, 1954-1974. (Folder 53: 1)
    Includes report by the organization critical of HUAC
  - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China. Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Folder 53: 2)
  - American Business Committee on National Priorities. Circulars and press releases, 1971 (Folder 53: 3)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Folder 53)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1971. (Folder 53: 4)
      Includes circular letters
    - American Civil Liberties Union issuances. Statements, leaflets, and circulars, 1949-1972 (Folder 53: 5)
    - American Civil Liberties Union serial issues (American Civil Liberties Union News; Civil Liberties; Open Forum), 1966-1973 (Folder 53: 6)
    - American Civil Liberties Union pamphlets and annual reports, 1955-1970. (Folder 53: 7)
      Includes The Case against the House Un-American Activities Committee; Academic Freedom and Civil Liberties of Students in Colleges and Universities; Clearing the Main Channels; The Federal Security Program; Liberty Is Always Unfinished Business
    - Material about the American Civil Liberties Union, 1939-1973. (Folder 54: 1-2)
      Clippings, newsletters, bulletins, journal articles, and pamphlets. Includes The A.C.L.U.: Lawyers Playing the Red Game; The ACLU Report: The Curious Story of the American Civil Liberties Union; Does the American Civil Liberties Union Serve the Communist Cause?; The Truth about the American Civil Liberties Union
  - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom. Pamphlet (Can You Name Them?), clipping, and list of sponsors, 1939-1940 (Folder 54: 3)
  - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. (Folder 54)
    See also Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born internal documents. Letters, reports, memoranda, and financial records, 1939-1967 (Folder 54: 4)
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born conferences. Programs, circular letters, and reports of proceedings (Folder 54)
      - 1939 (Folder 54: 5)
      - 1940 (Folder 54: 6)
      - 1941 (Folder 54: 7)
      - 1942 (Folder 54: 8)
      - 1943 (Folder 54: 9)
      - 1947 (Folder 54: 10)
      - 1948 (Folder 54: 11)
      - 1949 (Folder 54: 12)
      - 1951 (Folder 54: 13)
      - 1952 (Folder 54: 14)
      - 1953 (Folder 54: 15)
      - 1954 (Folder 54: 16)
      - 1955 (Folder 55: 1)
      - 1956 (Folder 55: 2)
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born issuances. Circular letters, statements, press releases, petitions, flyers, and leaflets, 1938-1973 (Folder 55: 3-4)
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born serial issues, 1947-1964. (Folder 55: 5)
      Includes The Lamp; Bulletin; Newsletter
    - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born pamphlets, 1947-1963. (Folder 55: 6)
      Includes Concentration Camps USA; The Deportation Terror; End Exile; In Defense of the Right to Defend Foreign Born Americans; In the Shadow of Liberty; The Legacy of Abner Green; Step-Children of a Nation: The Status of Mexican-Americans; The Walter-McCarran Law; The Walter-McCarran Law: Police State Terror against Foreign-Born Americans
    - Communist Party and related publications. Newspaper and journal articles, 1927-1956. (Folder 56: 1)
      Includes articles from Daily Worker and Digest of Soviet News
    - Miscellany. Clippings and other printed matter, HUAC staff notes, and Federal Bureau of Investigation report, 1942-1959 (Folder 56: 2)
  - American Committee for Representation at World Peace Congress. Printed announcement, 1950 (Folder 56: 3)
  - American Committee for Solidarity with the Vietnamese People. Flyers, 1969 (Folder 56: 4)
  - American Committee for Spanish Freedom. Letter and clipping, 1945-1946 (Folder 56: 5)
  - American Committee for Struggle against War. Printed statement, and pamphlet (The World Congress against War), 1932-1933 (Folder 56: 6)
  - American Committee for the Fourth International. Statement and serial issues (Bulletin of International Socialism), 1965 (Folder 56: 7)
  - American Committee of Jewish Writers, Artists and Scientists. Clipping and serial issues (New Currents), 1943-1948 (Folder 56: 8)
  - American Committee on Africa. Circular letters and brochures, 1969-1972 (Folder 56: 9)
  - American Committee to Save Refugees. Circulars, 1940 (Folder 56: 10)
  - American Communications Association. Circular letters and pamphlet (Why ACA Was Thrown Out of the CIO), 1941-ca. 1949 (Folder 56: 11)
  - American Council against Nazi Propaganda. Letter by Albert E. Kahn, 1939 (Folder 56: 12)
  - American Crusade to End Lynching. Leaflet, 1946 (Folder 56: 13)
  - American Dialog. Circular letters and serial issues (Folder 56)
    - 1964-1967 (Folder 56: 14)
    - 1968-1972 (Folder 56: 15)
  - American Documentary Films. Catalogs, 1969-1971 (Folder 56: 16)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations [AFL-CIO]. Clippings, pamphlet (Labor Unity), brochures and leaflets, 1955-1971 (Folder 56: 17)
  - American Federation of Teachers. Conference proceedings, serial issues (Washington, D.C. Teacher), and leaflets, 1929-1970. (Folder 56: 18)
    Includes proceedings of 6th, 7th and 8th Annual Conferences of Teachers in Workers' Education, 1929-1931
  - American Federation of Teachers (contd.) (Folder 57: 1)
  - American Forum for Socialist Education. Memorandum and Congressional hearing report, 1957 (Folder 57: 2)
  - American Friends of Cuba Association. Broadcast summary and Federal Bureau of Investigation report, 1966 (Folder 57: 3)
  - American Friends of the Chinese People. Serial issues (China Today), 1937-1941 (Folder 57: 4)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1972. (Folder 57: 5)
    - American Friends Service Committee reports, 1969-1973. (Folder 57: 6)
      Includes report on the Soviet Union and Czechoslovakia, and reports on imprisoned war resisters in the United States
    - American Friends Service Committee issuances, 1959-1974. (Folder 57: 7)
      Flyers, leaflets, serial issues (Quaker Service Bulletin), programs, and pamphlets. Includes Behind the Corporate Image (re General Electric Corporation), and Vietnam: Vital Interest or Tragic Mistake?
    - Clippings about the American Friends Service Committee, 1966-1972 (Folder 57: 8)
  - American Humanist Association. Leaflet, circular letters, newsletters, and serial issue (Humanist), 1962-1971 (Folder 57: 9)
  - American Independent Movement. Clipping, and newsletters (AIM), 1966-1969 (Folder 57: 10)
  - American Indian Movement. Bulletin, 1973 (Folder 57: 11)
  - American Institute for Marxist Studies [New York City] (Folder 57)
    - General. Correspondence (including circular letters), brochures, programs, and clippings, 1964-1971 (Folder 57: 12)
    - Newsletters (Folder 57)
      - 1968-1969 (Folder 57: 13)
      - 1970-1972 (Folder 58: 1)
  - American Jewish Conference on Soviet Jewry. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 58: 2)
  - American-Korean Friendship and Information Center [New York City] (Folder 58)
    - General. Correspondence, circular letters, flyers, clippings, and pamphlet (Operation War Shift), 1971-1974 (Folder 58: 3)
    - Korea Focus. Serial issues (Folder 58)
      - 1971-1972 (Folder 58: 4)
      - 1973-1976 (Folder 58: 5)
  - American Labor Party. Circulars, leaflets, clippings, and pamphlet (Negro Representation Now!), 1940-1952 (Folder 58: 6)
  - American League against War and Fascism (Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1933-1937. (Folder 58: 7)
    - American League against War and Fascism issuances, 1933-1937. (Folder 58: 8)
      Leaflets, flyers, program and proceedings of U.S. Congresses against War and Fascism, serial issues (Fight against War and Fascism), and pamphlets (California's Brown Book; Why Fascism Leads to War)
    - American League against War and Fascism petition for boycott of Japan with voluminous signatures (Chicago area), undated (Folder 58: 9)
    - Miscellany. Clippings and critical report on the American League against War and Fascism by Hillman M. Bishop, 1937-1939 (Folder 58: 10)
  - American League for Peace and Democracy (Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Folder 59: 1)
    - American League for Peace and Democracy issuances, 1938-1939. (Folder 59: 2)
      Statement, report, leaflets, flyers, and serial issues (Fight for Peace and Democracy)
    - Clippings, 1939-1954 (Folder 59: 3)
  - American League of Ex-Servicemen. Circular letter, 1935 (Folder 59: 4)
  - American Liberation League. Circulars and serial issues (Liberation USA), 1966 (Folder 59: 5)
  - American National Party. Leaflets, 1962 (Folder 59: 6)
  - American Nazi Party. Clipping, and HUAC report, 1967-1969 (Folder 59: 7)
  - American Negro Labor Congress. Reports, and letter by James W. Ford, 1928 (Folder 59: 8)
  - American Peace Crusade. (Folder 59)
    See also Southern California Peace Crusade
    - General. Circulars, leaflets, flyers, newsletters, and clippings, 1951-1955 (Folder 59: 9)
    - American Peace Crusader. Serial issues, 1951 (Folder 59: 10)
  - American Peace Mobilization. Letter, circulars, leaflets, flyers, clippings, and pamphlets (Conscription and the War; What Is APM?; Wives or Widows?), 1940-1941 (Folder 59: 11)
  - American Relief for Greek Democracy. Articles of incorporation, statements, press releases, circulars, memoranda, leaflets, and flyers, 1946-1947 (Folder 59: 12)
  - American Russian Institute [New York City] (Folder 60)
    - General. Flyers, clippings, and pamphlets (The Dean of Canterbury to the People of America: We Can Keep Peace; The Soviet Union Today: An Outline Study; We Pledge Peace: A Friendship Book), 1943-1955 (Folder 60: 1)
    - American Russian Institute serial issues (Folder 60)
      - American Quarterly on the Soviet Union, 1939-1940 (Folder 60: 2)
      - American Review on the Soviet Union. (Folder 60)
        - 1941-1942 (Folder 60: 3-4)
        - 1946-1947 (Folder 61: 1)
  - American Servicemen's Union [GI organization]. Flyers, clipping, serial issues (Bond), and pamphlet (Black Marines against the Brass), 1968-1971 (Folder 61: 2)
  - American Slav Congress. Leaflet, clipping, and printed articles, 1946-1948 (Folder 61: 3)
  - American Society for the Study of the German Democratic Republic. Correspondence, flyers, and printed appeal, 1970-1973 (Folder 61: 4)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers. Newsletter, 1956 (Folder 61: 5)
  - American Society to Defend Children. Flyer, 1966 (Folder 61: 6)
  - American Sociological Association. Clippings, 1967 (Folder 61: 7)
  - American-Soviet Science Society. Circular letter, and leaflet, 1946 (Folder 61: 8)
  - American Writers against the War in Vietnam. Printed appeals and clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 61: 9)
  - American Youth Congress. Circulars, flyers, pamphlet (Youngville, U.S.A.), and flyer critical of American Youth Congress, 1937-1938 (Folder 61: 10)
  - American Youth Festival Committee [re World Youth Festival]. Circulars, 1965 (Folder 61: 11)
  - American Youth for Democracy. Letter, leaflet, circulars, and clippings, 1944-1946 (Folder 61: 12)
  - Americans for Democracy in the Middle East. Clippings, 1967 (Folder 61: 13)
  - Americans for Democratic Action. Circulars, press releases, leaflets, flyers, and pamphlets (Putting Our House in Order: The Case against HUAC), 1962-1972 (Folder 61: 14)
  - Americans for Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policy. Flyers, printed articles, and printed report (China Survey), 1965-1966 (Folder 61: 15)
  - Americans Want to Know [re Cambodia]. Circulars, leaflet, and clippings, 1966 (Folder 61: 16)
  - Amex-Canada ["published by Americans exiled in Canada"]. Serial issues, 1972-1973 (Folder 61: 17)
  - Amnesty for Dissenters. Printed appeal, 1973 (Folder 61: 18)
  - Amnesty International. Circulars, 1969 (Folder 61: 19)
  - Anarchos. Serial issue, 1968 (Folder 61: 20)
  - Angry Arts against the War in Vietnam. Printed announcements and clippings, 1967 (Folder 61: 21)
  - Ann Arbor Defense Fund [University of Michigan]. Circulars, 1966 (Folder 61: 22)
  - Annapolis Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Circulars and clippings, 1966 (Folder 61: 23)
  - Another Mother for Peace. Circular letter, leaflet, and clipping, 1967-1969 (Folder 61: 24)
  - Anti-draft movement (General). Flyers, leaflets, printed articles, clippings, and HUAC memoranda, 1964-1968 (Folder 62: 1)
  - Anti-Escalation Committee. Flyer and clipping, 1967 (Folder 62: 2)
  - Anti-War Union. Leaflet, 1972 (Folder 62: 3)
  - Antithesis. Serial issue, 1965 (Folder 62: 4)
  - Appeal from Social Workers in the Greater Washington Area [re Vietnam War]. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 62: 5)
  - April Action [Philadelphia]. Newsletter and clipping, 1969 (Folder 62: 6)
  - Aptheker, Herbert. (Folder 62: 7)
    See also Herbert Aptheker Testimonial Dinner Committee, and Independent Citizens Committee to Elect Herbert Aptheker. Election campaign flyers, and clippings, 1966
  - Army Information Company. Printed article, 1965 (Folder 62: 8)
  - Aronowitz, Stanley. Photocopy of index card file, 1962-1971 (Folder 62: 9)
  - Artists Protest Committee. Printed appeal and clippings, 1966-1968 (Folder 62: 10)
  - Assembly of Unrepresented People [Washington, D.C.]. Printed appeal, clippings, printed articles, Congressional speech, police reports, and HUAC memorandum and report, 1965-1966 (Folder 62: 11)
  - Association for Friendship and Cultural Relations/USA-USSR. Circulars, 1972-1974 (Folder 62: 12)
  - Atlanta Peace Action Coalition. Circulars, 1971 (Folder 62: 13)
  - Atlanta Workshop in Nonviolence. Circulars, 1968 (Folder 62: 14)
  - Atlantis Books [Hollywood]. Catalogs, undated (Folder 62: 15)
  - Attica Defense Committee. Circulars, serial issues (Attica News), and clippings, 1971-1974 (Folder 62: 16)
  - Attica Fund. Pamphlets (Voices from Inside; We Are Attica), ca. 1972 (Folder 62: 17)
  - August 6-9 Committee [Berkeley/Oakland]. Flyers, 1966 (Folder 62: 18)
  - August 9th Nagasaki Day Committee. Flyer, 1966 (Folder 62: 19)
  - Authors' Guild. Letter and leaflet, 1944 (Folder 62: 20)
  - Badger for Peace [re Vietnam War]. Flyers, undated (Folder 63: 1)
  - Badillo, Herman. Press releases, 1971 (Folder 63: 2)
  - Baehler, John. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 63: 3)
  - Baez, Joan. Clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 63: 4)
  - Baltimore Committee of Clergymen Concerned about Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 63: 5)
  - Baltimore Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 63: 6)
  - Baltimore Defense Committee [re Catonsville 9]. Flyers, undated (Folder 63: 7)
  - Baltimore Interfaith Peace Mission. Printed appeal and clippings, 1967-1968 (Folder 63: 8)
  - Baltimore Teachers Concerned about Vietnam. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 63: 9)
  - Bangladesh. Flyers, printed articles, and memorandum re solidarity with people of Bangladesh, 1971 (Folder 63: 10)
  - Bar Committee against Test Oaths for Lawyers. Report, statement, and correspondence, 1949 (Folder 63: 11)
  - Baty, Donald. Clipping and HUAC memorandum, 1967 (Folder 63: 12)
  - Bay Area Committee for the Vietnam Ad [San Francisco Bay Area]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 63: 13)
  - Bay Area Inter-Universities Committee on Foreign Policy [San Francisco Bay Area]. Printed appeal, 1965 (Folder 63: 14)
  - Bay Area Organizing Committee for Draft Resistance [San Francisco Bay Area]. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 63: 15)
  - Bay Area Peace Action Council [San Francisco Bay Area]. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 63: 16)
  - Bay Area Student Committee for the Abolition of the House Committee on Un-American Activities [San Francisco Bay Area]. Pamphlets (In Search of Truth; The Meisenbach Case), 1960-1961 (Folder 63: 17)
  - Bayh, Birch. Press releases, 1971 (Folder 63: 18)
  - Becker, Norma. Photocopy of index card file, 1965-1971 (Folder 63: 19)
  - Behavioral Scientists for Peace. Press release, 1961 (Folder 63: 20)
  - Beloit College Peace Education Group. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 63: 21)
  - Berkeley Anti-Draft Union. Flyers, 1967 (Folder 63: 22)
  - Berkeley Free Press. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 63: 23)
  - Berrigan, Daniel and Philip. Includes Catonsville 9, Harrisburg 13, and Harrisburg Defense Committee. Flyers, circulated documents, petitions (with signatures), clippings, printed articles, and pamphlet (The Trial of the Catonsville Nine), 1970-1973 (Folder 63: 24)
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation. Includes International War Crimes Tribunal sponsored by the Foundation. Printed appeal, flyers, radio broadcast summary, printed article, and clippings, 1964-1967 (Folder 63: 25)
  - Bethany Methodist Church [city uncertain]. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 63: 26)
  - Bethune, Mary McLeod. Correspondence and clipping, 1939-1940 (Folder 63: 27)
  - Bevel, James. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 63: 28)
  - Bill of Rights Conference (New York City, 1949). Leaflet, list of sponsors, and HUAC memorandum (Folder 63: 29)
  - Bill of Rights Conference (New York City, 1971). Program, list of sponsors, circulated documents, letter by George McGovern, and HUAC memorandum (Folder 63: 30)
  - Binder, Arthur. Flyer, 1965 (Folder 63: 31)
  - Birthday Committee for Henry Winston. Invitation, 1971 (Folder 63: 32)
  - Biweekly Information/Action Report [Ann Arbor, Michigan]. Bulletin, 1966 (Folder 63: 33)
  - Black and Spanish-Speaking Anti-Draft Front. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 63: 34)
  - Black Anti-Draft Union. Flyer and clipping, 1967-1968 (Folder 63: 35)
  - Black Liberation Army. New York City Police Department Intelligence Division report, including copies of Black Liberation Army internal documents and printed article, 1973 (Folder 63: 36)
  - Black Liberation Party. Serial issue (Liberation News), 1971 (Folder 63: 37)
  - Black Panther Party (Folder 63)
    - Black Panther Party issuances, 1969-1970. (Folder 63: 38)
      Flyers, press releases, and pamphlets (Capitalism Plus Dope Equals Genocide; Education and Revolution; On the Ideology of the Black Panther Party)
    - Black Panther. Serial issues, 1969-1974 (Folder 64: 1)
    - Defense group issuances. Circular letters, flyers, reports and serial issues (Folder 64)
      - General, 1968-1970. (Folder 64: 2)
        Includes Soledad Brothers Defense Committee
      - Panther 21 Trial, 1970-1971 (Folder 64: 3)
      - HISC staff studies of Black Panther Party, 1969 (Folder 64: 4)
      - Reports by other organizations on the Black Panther Party, 1968-1971. (Folder 64: 5)
        Includes reports by Federal Bureau of Investigation, Library of Congress Legislative Reference Service, American Jewish Committee, and Church League of America
      - Printed articles and clippings about the Black Panther Party, 1968-1974. (Folder 64: 6)
        Includes Playboy interview of Huey Newton
  - Black Scholar Book Club. Catalog, 1972 (Folder 64: 7)
  - Black United Action Front [New York City]. Flyers, 1967 (Folder 64: 8)
  - Blacks (General) (Folder 65)
    - Miscellaneous black or support group issuances (Folder 65)
      - Flyers, leaflets, circular letters, appeals and petitions, 1942-1974. (Folder 65: 1)
        Includes speech by Leroi Jones
      - Pamphlets and serial issues, 1936-1972. (Folder 65: 2)
        Includes pamphlets Equal Justice Under Law, Freedom Is Everybody's Job!, Voting Restrictions in the 13 Southern States, and legal briefs for Scottsboro Boys; and serial issues American Negro and Negro Worker
    - Material about blacks, 1947-1972. (Folder 65: 3)
      Clippings, printed articles, and HUAC memoranda
  - Blacks United to Resist Now [BURN; Chicago]. Flyer, undated (Folder 65: 4)
  - Blake, Eugene Carson. Clippings and press release, 1966 (Folder 65: 5)
  - Bliven, Bruce. Letter by Bliven to HUAC, 1944 (Folder 65: 6)
  - Bond, Julian. Clippings and circular letter, 1966-ca. 1970. (Folder 65: 7)
    See also Citizens Committee for Julian Bond
  - Braden, Carl. Circular letter and clemency appeal petitions, 1961 (Folder 65: 8)
    See also Southern Conference Educational Fund
  - Bring the Troops Home Now Newsletter. Serial issues, circular letters, informant's report, flyer, clipping, and HUAC notes, 1965-1967 (Folder 65: 9)
  - British Vietnam Committee. Pamphlet (Vietnam: United States Dirty War), 1965 (Folder 65: 10)
  - Broadhead, Richard Wright. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 65: 11)
  - Brook, Calvin. Circular letter, Congressional hearing excerpts, and photocopy of index card file, 1949-1957 (Folder 65: 12)
  - Brooklyn College Ad Hoc Committee for Petition to the President and Members of the Congress on the War in Vietnam. Petition, 1967 (Folder 65: 13)
  - Brooklyn Forum Committee. Petition re Vietnam War, undated (Folder 65: 14)
  - Brooklyn Residents for Peace. Flyers, 1966 (Folder 65: 15)
  - Brown, Anthony. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 65: 16)
  - Bryn Mawr College Alumnae Ad Hoc Committee. Printed appeal re Vietnam War, 1968 (Folder 65: 17)
  - Buchman, Harold. Correspondence, financial records, and Soviet passport, 1964-1971 (Folder 65: 18)
  - Burak, Martin. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 65: 19)
  - Burchett, Wilfred. Circular letter and clippings, 1965-1967 (Folder 65: 20)
  - Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace and New National Priorities (Folder 65)
    - Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace and New National Priorities issuances. Printed appeals, circular letters, newsletters, and brochures (Folder 65)
      - 1967-1969 (Folder 65: 21)
      - 1970 (Folder 66: 1)
      - 1971 (Folder 66: 2)
      - 1972 (Folder 66: 3)
    - Clippings, 1967-1969 (Folder 66: 4)
  - Businessmen's Committee on Vietnam. Circular letter and appeal, ca. 1965 (Folder 66: 5)
  - California. Assembly. Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights. Hearing transcript, and HUAC memorandum critical of the California legislative subcommittee, 1957-1958 (Folder 66: 6)